# Chase Seltzner

chase.seltz21@gmail.com ❖ (480) 881-5029 ❖ Mesa, AZ ❖ www.Seltzner.com

#### **SKILLS**

React/HTML/CSS/JS/TS
Node.js/ASP.NET APIs
SQL/Database Design
Unit/E2E Testing
Version Control
Mobile Applications
Leadership
Skillful in creating reactive, responsive, typed, and accessible web applications.
Proficient in creating and consuming REST APIs with modern technologies.
Experience creating and using complex database designs.
Proficient with modern testing frameworks such as Jest, Cypress, and xUnit.
Knowledgeable using git branches, merges, and rebases.
Familiar with mobile application development using Kotlin and React Native.
Ability to communicate effectively on large teams, and lead when called upon.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Medical Scribe Mar 2021 – Nov 2022

Essential Scribe Phoenix, AZ

 Accurately document emergency room patient records in real time, ensuring comprehensive and organized medical records for over 1,500 patients.

Continuously engage with doctors and nurses to ensure patient's medical records are accurate and up to date.

Head Supervisor Sept 2017 – Dec 2020

Gordon Dining & Event Center

Madison, WI

- Lead a team of hundreds of student employees on UW-Madison's largest dining and event center.
- As head supervisor, I managed our student employee base, student hiring processes, interviews, discipline, inventory, and orders.
  - o **Key Results:** Over 2000 daily transactions, with over 200 student employees, making Gordon Dining & Event Center the highest volume dining center at UW-Madison.
- Fostered a positive work environment by listening to employee concerns and providing support.

# Undergraduate Researcher

Dec 2018 - Dec 2020

Holden Laboratory

Madison, WI

- Conduct protein crystallization experiments and analyze X-ray diffraction data to determine the 3D structures of proteins and protein-ligand complexes.
  - o See published papers: <a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/pro.4139">https://doi.org/10.1002/pro.4502</a>.

## **EDUCATION**

## University of Wisconsin - Madison

December 2020

Bachelor of Science - Biology, Bachelor of Science - Economics

Madison, WI

- **GPA: 3.83/4.0**; Graduated with distinction in top 20% of class.
- Undergraduate researcher Holden Laboratory.

## **INTERESTS**

Photography, hiking, and fountain pens.